(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
昔々あるところにチョコレートの魔法がかかったお城がありました。
Once upon a time, there was a castle under a chocolate spell.
お城の本当の姿はとっても可愛い姿をしているのに、
The castle's true form was very cute, but...
今は魔法のチョコレートのせいで可愛いからは程遠いダークな雰囲気のお城です。
now, because of the magic chocolate, it's a dark-themed castle far from being cute.
そこに、一人の悪魔がやってきました。
Then, a single demon arrived.
「あら、とってもかっこいいお城じゃない」
“Oh, what a very cool castle.”
「ここで私の歌とダンスを世に届けるのも悪くないわね」
“It wouldn't be bad to share my songs and dances with the world here.”
そう言うと、悪魔は仲間達と一緒にクールでセクシーなライブを始めました。
With that, the demon started a cool and sexy live performance with her friends.
するとどうでしょう。
Then, what do you know?
ライブの熱気で、瞬く間にお城のチョコレートが溶けていくではありませんか。
The excitement of the live performance melted the castle's chocolate in the blink of an eye.
本来の姿を取り戻した、可愛いお城で今晩は...
In the cute castle that regained its original form, tonight...
あ...
Ah...
うーん...
Hmm...
ば、番長？
Ba- Banchou?
もう、せっかく読んであげてたのに。
Geez, I was reading it just for you.
寝ちゃったの？
Did you fall asleep?
ふふふっ。
Fufufu.
あらあら、寝顔も可愛いわね。
My, my, even your sleeping face is cute.
むにゃむにゃ...
Mumble mumble...
どんな夢見てるのかしら。
I wonder what kind of dream you're having.
Got Cheat
言い訳ばかりの光
Light full of nothing but excuses
月明かりの代わり
Substituting for the moonlight
見下ろした街並み
The cityscape I looked down upon
少しも光れない
Can't shine even a little bit
嗅ぎつけておきもち
Sniffing out your feelings
この時間惜しい
This time is precious
焦らすの嗜み
Teasing is my pastime
そういうことね
That's how it is
いい？
Ready?
見つめて
Stare at me
もっと飲ませて
Let me drink more
もっと言わせて
Let me say more
恥ずかしい
How embarrassing
君はどこにでもいるボーイ
You're a boy found anywhere
なのに胸がヒリつくわ
Yet my heart is stinging
いけるとこまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can
揺れるリンクも染めて Got Cheat
Dye the swaying link too, Got Cheat
これはありふれている日常
This is a commonplace daily life
...繰り返したいわ
...I want to repeat it
行けるとこまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can go
甘い誘惑癖になってるガチ
Sweet temptation, it's becoming a habit, for real
君のせいでも僕のせいでも
Whether it's your fault or my fault
どちらでもガチ
Either way, for real
確かめてよ相性
Please check our compatibility
ただ求めて欲しい
I just want you to want me
バレるまで過ち
An error until it's found out
よそ見はしないでいい
It's okay, don't look away
もっと合わせて
Match me more
もっと先まで
Further ahead
もっと回して
Spin it more
もっと言わせて
Let me say it more
僕を慰めている問い
A question that's comforting me
思考焼き切れるまで
Until my thoughts burn out
行けるとこまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can go
震えるリンクそう破ってるガチ
A trembling link, yeah, it's breaking, for real
君はどこにでもいる僕
You're everywhere, me
なのに胸がヒリつくわ
And yet my chest stings
行けるとこまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can go
震えるリンクもしめてるガチ
Even the trembling link is closing, for real
これはありふれている理論
This is a common theory
だけど繰り返したいわ
But I want to repeat it
行けるとこまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can go
甘い誘惑癖になってるガチ
Sweet temptation, it's becoming a habit, for real
君のせいでも僕のせいでも
Whether it's your fault or my fault
何度でもガチ
Over and over again, for real
はーい！ということで
Hi! And with that
癒月ちょこ生誕祭ライブ2025、始まりましたー！イエーイ！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Live 2025 has begun! Yay!
1曲目は「Gachi」
The first song was "Gachi"
Got Cheatをみんな覚えてたー？
Did everyone remember "Got Cheat"?
ねぇどうだったかな？どうだったかなー？
Hey, how was it? How was it?
そして今回のライブのハッシュタグはこちら！
And the hashtag for this live is this!
ドドドドーン！
Ta-daaa!
まぁぜひぜひスクショとかね、感想をどんどんXにポストしてください！
Well, please do take screenshots and post your impressions on X!
さてさて冒頭で番長に読み聞かせしてたチョコなんですけど
Now then, Choco was reading a story to Bancho at the beginning
みんな内容覚えてる？
Does everyone remember the content?
昔々あるところにチョコレートの魔法がかかったお城がありました。
Once upon a time, in a certain place, there was a castle under a chocolate spell.
おやおや？チョコレートの魔法がかかったお城？
Oh? A castle under a chocolate spell?
見て見てこのステージ！
Look, look at this stage!
今回のステージはチョコレートでコーティングされているお城ですねー！
This stage is a castle coated in chocolate!
ね、ビターの感じがしてめちゃめちゃカッコよくないですか？
Doesn't it look really cool with that bitter feel?
ま、この後ねどうなるかはお楽しみにー！
Well, look forward to what happens after this!
うーん、番長は今も部室ですやすやなのかな？
Hmm, I wonder if Bancho is still sleeping soundly in the clubroom?
なんて。
Just kidding.
あ！
Ah!
今回はねこの後は、いっぱいチョコの仲間たちも呼んでるので
For this live, after this, I've invited many of Choco's friends
みんなで一緒に盛り上がっていきましょう！
So let's all get excited together!
それでは最初のゲストさんはこちらです！
Now then, here is our first guest!
次の曲へゴー！
Let's go to the next song!
ビターチョコデコレーション
作詞・作曲：syudou
Bitter Choco Decoration
Lyrics/Composition: syudou
人に疑われないように　愛されないように　期待されないように
So as not to be suspected, loved, or expected from.
かと言って角が立たないように　気取らぬように　目立たぬように
But also to not cause friction, to not be pretentious, to not stand out.
誰一人傷つけぬように　いじめぬように　殺さぬように
So as not to hurt anyone, to not bully, to not kill.
かと言って偽善が出ないように　威張らぬように
But also to not seem hypocritical, to not be bossy.
軽いジョークやリップサービスも忘れぬように
And not forgetting light jokes and lip service.
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
Always smiling and spreading charm.
ビターチョコデコレーション　兎角言わずにたんと召し上がれ
Bitter Choco Decoration. Don't say a word and eat plenty.
ビターチョコデコレーション　食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
Bitter Choco Decoration. You must fix your picky eating.
頭空っぽのその後に　残る心が本物なら
If the heart that remains after the head is empty is real...
きっと君だって同じこと　ところで一つ伺いますが
Surely you are the same. By the way, I have one question.
先日どこかでやった嫌
The unpleasantness we did somewhere the other day.
無駄に自我を晒さぬように　話さぬように　分からぬように
So as not to expose my ego unnecessarily, to not speak, to not be understood.
でも絶対口を閉じぬように　笑わすよりは笑われるように
But never closing my mouth, to be laughed at rather than to make laugh.
人をちゃんと敬うように　崇めるように　称えるように
To respect people properly, to revere them, to praise them.
でも決して病みにならぬように　ふざけないように
But never to become sick/dark, to not mess around.
油断させて周知徹底またヘコラヘコラ言っちゃって
Lulling into a false sense of security, widespread thoroughness, saying "yes, yes" again.
前髪超越最強じゃんとかどうでもいいのに言っちゃって
Saying stuff like "your bangs are beyond the strongest" even though I don't care.
毎晩毎晩猛省回収　常時社会の集団心理
Every night, collecting deep reflections. Always the group psychology of society.
逃げ出して発狂しないように　ビターチョコデコレーション
So as not to run away and go crazy. Bitter Choco Decoration.
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す　ビターチョコデコレーション
Sometimes lonely love stains you. Bitter Choco Decoration.
立つ鳥の跡きっとクソの跡
The traces of a departing bird are surely traces of shit.
初めはあんなにいたそうな　大幻想を並べたが
At first, they seemed to be there, lining up grand fantasies.
いやいやいやもう好きのうち　いやはやしかし今日が初めてで
No, no, no, while I still like it. My goodness, but today is the first time.
こんな問われ方君センスあるよ
To be questioned like this, you've got sense.
恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション
In the season of love, Bitter Choco Decoration.
恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
With the feeling of love, Bitter Choco Decoration.
F U C K Y O U　ビターチョコデコレーション
F U C K Y O U Bitter Choco Decoration.
皆が望む理想に憧れて　ビターチョコデコレーション
Longing for the ideal that everyone wants. Bitter Choco Decoration.
個性や毒は全部焼き払い　ビターチョコデコレーション
Burning away all individuality and poison. Bitter Choco Decoration.
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め　ビターチョコデコレーション
Killing greed and ego and burying them in the ground. Bitter Choco Decoration.
僕は大人にやっと成ったよパパ
I've finally become an adult, Papa.
明日もきっとこの先も　地獄は続くどこまでも
Tomorrow and surely from now on, hell will continue forever.
ああだからどうか今だけは　子供の頃の気持ちのままで
Ah, so please, just for now, stay with the feelings of childhood.
意地も通さずにやってこうぜ　思い出したあの時の
Let's go without even pushing our will. I remembered back then.
生真面目そうな　やっぱいいや
That serious-looking... never mind.
「好きですか？」の何代目に　笑顔で返すしかできない
To the "Do you like me?" of which generation, I can only respond with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように　私の答えを君は待っている
As if teased by a devil, you are waiting for my answer.
Secret Class
作詞・作曲・編曲：奏音69
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Kanon69
放課後の教室に　君だけを残す時間が好き
I like the time when only you are left in the classroom after school.
二人きりになっても　許される訳になるでしょう
Even if we are alone together, there's a reason it's allowed, right?
ねぇ　きっとあの子のように　隣を歩けないのは
Hey, the reason I can't walk beside you like that girl...
まっすぐに揺れる白衣　それが二人の距離だから
Is the white coat swaying straightly; that is the distance between us.
熱くなるほど幼い　心が暴れちゃわないように
So that my heart doesn't go wild, the more it heats up with childishness.
君にとっての大人になるふりして担う　秘密のクラス
Pretending to be an adult for you, I take on... the secret class.
「好きですか？」の何代目に　笑顔で返すしかできない
To the "Do you like me?" of which generation, I can only respond with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように　私の答えを君は待っている
As if teased by a devil, you are waiting for my answer.
淡い恋でしたて アルバムにしてあげたほうがいい
It was a faint love, better to keep it in an album
終わらぬチャイムがいつになるか それがたまらなく怖い
I wonder when the never-ending chime will ring, it's unbearably scary
きっとあの子のほうが君にお似合いだよねなんて
I bet that girl is a better match for you, and so on...
去る制服 揺れる白衣 ふとした言葉も傷つけてしまう
Departing uniform, swaying white coat, even casual words end up hurting
失うものが何もない 無邪気な目で苦しめないで
Don't torture me with those innocent eyes that have nothing to lose
君のテストに大人さえも答えられない言葉に詰まる
Even adults can't answer your tests, I'm at a loss for words
好きだよと全部捨てて 抱き寄せたいしまいたいのに
Even though I want to throw everything away, tell you "I love you," and hold you close
そんな強い心じゃいられない 私の答えに×をつけて
I can't be that strong, so please put an "X" on my answer
これでいい 君のためにそう決めたのに
This is fine, I decided that for your sake, and yet...
制服 揺らめく白衣 思わず君を引き止める
Uniform, swaying white coat, I instinctively stop you
好きですか？の難題に許されない答えを書いた
I wrote an unforgivable answer to the difficult question "Do you love me?"
君の明日を縛るだけの独りよがりな恋の約束
A self-centered promise of love that only binds your tomorrow
さよなら君の悲しむ顔 もう見送らなくていいなら
Goodbye, if I don't have to see your sad face off anymore
たとえ悪魔と呼ばれてもいい 甘く蕩けるような一時をあなたに
Even if I'm called a devil, I'll give you a moment that feels like it's melting sweetly
呼吸並べて見なほらLiar
Line up your breaths and look, you're a liar
理屈だなんてゴミ箱へ
Throw logic into the trash
身に覚えあるんでしょAnswer
You remember it, don't you? Answer
チクチク痛いのね
It's prickly and painful, isn't it?
エゴイズムに躍らされて
Dancing to the rhythm of egoism
蝕まれてく甘い甘い
Being eaten away, sweet, sweet
君に噛み付く悪魔でも
Even if I'm a devil that bites you
癒してあげましょう
I will heal you
お目覚めですか？
Are you awake?
Ding Dong Ding Dong 響け声 Ding Dong 笑えハッハッと叫んで
Ding Dong Ding Dong, let your voice ring out, Ding Dong, laugh and shout "Ha ha!"
Ding Dong Ding Dong 鳴らせよ Ding Dong 病むの五臓六腑 病むの五臓六腑
Ding Dong Ding Dong, ring it out, Ding Dong, it hurts my very soul
噛みつきゃしないわ
I won't bite you
慰めもしないわ
I won't comfort you either
私の胸明日から No Distance
From my heart tomorrow, No Distance
No Distance
闇に混ぜて甘いチョコレート溶かして
Mixed in the darkness, melt the sweet chocolate
錆びた鎖繋いで解いて
Connect the rusty chains, then unbind them
仮面被って瞳を隠して
Put on a mask and hide your eyes
傷が痛いのね
The wound hurts, doesn't it?
願望イズムに躍らされて
Dancing to the rhythm of desire-ism
蝕まれてく甘い甘い
Being eaten away, sweet, sweet
間違えていた優しくても
I was mistaken, even if I was kind
癒してあげましょう
I will heal you
あ、まだダメですか？
Oh, is it still no good?
Ding Dong Ding Dong 狂わせ Ding Dong 最期にハッハッと叫んで
Ding Dong Ding Dong, drive me crazy, Ding Dong, shout "Ha ha!" at the end
Ding Dong Ding Dong 迷わず Ding Dong 冷める前に口づけを
Ding Dong Ding Dong, without hesitation, Ding Dong, give me a kiss before it cools down
Ding Dong Ding Dong 響け声 Ding Dong 笑えハッハッと叫んで
Ding Dong Ding Dong, let your voice ring out, Ding Dong, laugh and shout "Ha ha!"
Ding dong ding dong
鳴らせよ ding dong
Let it ring, ding dong
揺らぐおさきに
Before the trembling...
病むのがおさきか
...is it before falling ill?
噛みつき おしのびを
Biting on a secret visit
慰めもしないわ
I won't even comfort you
私のものね
You are mine
飽きたら No distance
When I'm bored, No distance
放課後 甘い日差し
After school, the sweet sunlight...
カーテンが揺れる君の声
The curtains sway to the sound of your voice
チクタク 足音だけでわかる
Tick-tock, I can tell just by your footsteps
今日はどんな味が欲しい？
What kind of flavor do you want today?
囁く悪魔の誘惑 誘惑
The whispering devil's temptation... temptation
Sickbay 待ち合わせ Mistake な予感
Meeting at the sickbay, a premonition of a mistake
扉開けて さあこっちおいで
Open the door, now come over here
教科書に載っていない この気持ちはなんですか？
What is this feeling that's not in the textbook?
可愛い可愛い顔見せて
Show me your cute, cute face
Sickbay 会いましょう Mistake しちゃう
Let's meet at the sickbay, I'll make a mistake
永遠に続け 時間よ止まって
Continue forever, time please stop...
教授じゃ見せられない 笑顔の秘密は
The secret of the smile that a professor can't show
甘い甘いお菓子あげる
I'll give you sweet, sweet candy
囁く悪魔の誘惑 いかが？
The whispering devil's temptation... How is it?
病のリズムを 呼び越していく
Calling out the rhythm of the illness
聞かせて もっと君のこと
Let me hear more about you
触れる視線で 身体中
All over my body with your touching gaze
騒ぐの もう止まらないくらい
Getting rowdy, to the point where it won't stop
秘密のパスワードに 後には戻れない
With the secret password, there's no going back
目を開けて 恥じらって 手を振って 見つめあって
Open your eyes, be shy, wave your hand, look at each other
永遠の 楽園に 誘う 愛の言葉を
Leading you to an eternal paradise, words of love
耳元で 囁いて あげる
I'll whisper them in your ear...
Sickbay 待ってるわ Mistake な時間
I'm waiting at the sickbay, a mistaken time
扉閉めて もっと近付いて
Close the door, come closer
神様も止められない この気持ちの正体を
The true nature of this feeling that even God can't stop
知らないふりは もうできない
I can't pretend not to know anymore
Sickbay 最後 Mistake しましょう
Sickbay, the end, let's make a mistake
永遠はここにあるって信じて
Believe that eternity is here...
君にしか見せられない 笑顔の裏側
The back side of the smile that I can only show to you
甘い甘い果実あげる
I'll give you sweet, sweet fruit
囁く悪魔の誘惑 もっといかが？
The whispering devil's temptation... How about more?
いつでもここで待ってる My cute junior
I'll always be waiting here, my cute junior
おどろどろ 季節 駆け足で好き
Eerie season, I like it in a hurry
純白 雲 色を変える
Pure white clouds changing color
真っ赤な聖なる季節 悪夢にそっとして
Crimson holy season, leave the nightmare alone
漆黒の雲 覆い歩く
Jet-black clouds covering the path
雪降るツリーに 欲張りなお願いの山
On the snowy tree, a pile of greedy wishes
欲しいと言われると
When you tell me you want it...
いじわるしたくなっちゃうな
I feel like being mean
ちゃんと お願い して
Ask properly
Nobody Christmas 悪い子にはご褒美なしさ
Nobody Christmas! No rewards for bad kids
サンタより悪魔はいかが？ 望みを叶えてあげる
How about a devil instead of Santa? I'll grant your wish
また罠にはまった？
Did you get caught in the trap again?
小春日和 welcome
A warm winter day, welcome
To my spooky scary sickbay
Say yeah!
もはやストパニも
Even Stopani is now...
もう私のもの
...already mine.
もちろん そこに君も
And of course, you too.
あれこれ持って
Bring this and that.
目移りして困ってない？
Aren't you having trouble deciding?
そんな欲しいもの
Those things you want,
リストアップしておきました
I've made a list of them.
欲望
Your desires,
曝け出して
...lay them all bare.
のーばでぃーくりすます
Nobody Christmas
スニーカーの下に
Under your sneakers,
びっくり箱
...a jack-in-the-box.
驚いた表情はケーキよりデリシャスで
Your surprised face is more delicious than cake.
もっと見せて その表情
Show me more of that expression.
We wish you a Merry Chuchin
いい子ぶってるだけでしょ
You're just pretending to be a good child, aren't you?
隙をみせちゃってるんでしょ
You're showing your weakness.
プレゼントもういらないでしょ
You don't need presents anymore, do you?
だって私たちいれば満足でしょ
Because having us is enough for you, right?
その靴下の中に
Inside those stockings,
甘い誘惑イン
...sweet temptation, in.
諦めておいで
Give up and come here.
のーばでぃー
Nobody
のーばでぃーくりすます
Nobody Christmas
悪い子が夜更かししてる クリスマスに
Naughty children staying up late on Christmas.
クソガキにあげない
I won't give anything to the brats.
甘い甘いお仕置きを
Instead, a sweet, sweet punishment.
聖夜の前でいい子のフリして
Pretending to be good before the holy night,
アメもらうおバカさんなんて
...you fools getting candy.
甘いんですほらほら喜んで
It's sweet, see? Now be happy.
恐怖と幻あげちゃうね
I'll give you terror and illusions.
のーばでぃーくりすます
Nobody Christmas
...踊ろう
...Let's dance.
巡り会う糸はきっと 絡まる予報になって
The threads that meet will surely get entangled.
リアルで感じる熱は 本物の誘惑
The heat felt in reality is a true temptation.
時々高鳴る言葉も 速度が追いつけない
Sometimes words that race can't keep up with the speed.
期待の先に映る君がいて
You are there, reflected beyond expectation.
目に見えないメロディが 弾ける気がしたの
I felt an invisible melody burst forth.
ときめきはいつまでも 変わらない夢の証でしょう
The heartthrob will always be proof of an unchanging dream.
願い事集めてく カラフルに色づくストーリー
Gathering wishes, a story that colors colorfully.
それじゃ パシャっと 決めポーズ リズムに合わせて ダンス ダンス 踊ろう 踏み出して
Well then, strike a pose! To the rhythm, dance, dance, let's dance, step forward.
天使のハートで見せつけていこう これでもう大人と同じだね
Show it off with an angel's heart, now you're just like an adult.
最後は ギュっと 決めポーズ リズムに合わせて ダンス ダンス 踊ろう 駆け抜けて
Finally, strike a pose tight! To the rhythm, dance, dance, let's dance, run through.
天使の微笑みドキドキさせて これでもう大人と同じだね
Make hearts race with an angel's smile, now you're just like an adult.
ダラダラしてたら お昼まで
Lazing around until noon,
寝不足ヘトヘト お腹グー
...exhausted from lack of sleep, stomach growling.
集まってカフェで決め手 アンズ飴 最後であげた
Meeting at a café, the clincher, apricot candy given at the end.
塗ったり 編んだり 案外のんびり悪くないね 夢中中
Painting, knitting, it's surprisingly relaxing and not bad, lost in it.
時々霞む心も 真相まだ追いつけない
Sometimes the hazy heart still can't reach the truth.
悪戯に微笑む君がいて
You are there, smiling mischievously.
駆け足で届けたいの 魔法みたいにずっと
I want to deliver it at a run, forever like magic.
友達はいつまでも 忘れない想いを広げて
Friends will forever spread thoughts they won't forget.
どこまでも続いていく 同じ未来を見つめたい
Continuing everywhere, I want to look at the same future.
きっと 夢の中で描いた この瞬間は君だけのために
Surely, this moment drawn in a dream is just for you.
身体　私のココロの距離を繋ぐ糸
Body... the thread connecting the distance of my heart.
準備はOK
Ready to go!
それじゃぱっと　あざとくポーズを合わせて
Then, quickly, let's strike a cute pose together.
ダンスダンス　踊ろう輝いて
Dance, dance! Let's dance and shine.
天使の言葉で虜にしていく
I'll captivate you with an angel's words.
これでもかお揃いね
We're perfectly in sync.
最後はぎゅっと　キメポーズ　心に訪ねて
Finally, a tight finishing pose, ask your heart.
ダンスダンス　踊ろう飛び込んで
Dance, dance! Let's dance and dive in.
天使の微笑みドキドキさせて
Let an angel's smile make your heart race.
これでもかお揃いだね
We're perfectly in sync, aren't we?
ChocoLove
作詞・作曲・編曲：Junky
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Junky
Ah, ah, sweet stars...
聞いて会いたいの　飛んでって
Listen, I want to see you, so fly away.
少し困るくらいにお願い
Please, just a little bit too much.
ねぇ　ちゃんと聞いてみて　受け取って
Hey, listen carefully and accept it.
甘くとろけちゃうような時間を
A time that's so sweet it melts away.
疲れてる顔して
You have a tired face.
いつもたくさん頑張ってるね
You're always working so hard, aren't you?
もう全て投げ捨てて
Just throw everything else away.
全部食べてあげようか
Shall I eat it all up for you?
よそ見なんて嫌だよ
I don't want you looking elsewhere.
ちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
You have to keep your eyes on me.
目と目が合うでしょう
Our eyes will meet, right?
照れちゃうくらい見つめてね
Gaze at me until you're embarrassed.
一途　夢中にさせて
Single-mindedly, let me make you crazy for me.
一途　見つけてね
Single-mindedly, please find me.
合言葉　虜にしちゃうな
The password... I'll captivate you.
急拍数　急上昇
My heart rate is soaring.
好きだよ
I love you.
痛いの痛いの飛んでけ
Pain, pain, go away!
不安な顔より笑顔見せて
Show me a smile instead of that worried face.
ねぇ　ちゃんと聞いてみて　受け取って
Hey, listen carefully and accept it.
甘いチョコのような時間を
A time as sweet as chocolate.
ここに痛いの痛いの　もう困っちゃう
It hurts right here, I'm at a loss.
不意打ちにちょっとときめいて
My heart fluttered a bit from the surprise.
じらしちゃうわよ　ダメもうちょっと
I'm going to tease you, no, just a bit more.
君の声をもっと聴かせて
Let me hear your voice even more.
不安なんて抱えて
Carrying anxieties like that...
らしくないなんて思ってた
I thought it wasn't like me.
全部全部丸ごと
Everything, the whole lot.
包み込んで溶かしてあげる
I'll wrap it up and melt it all away.
どうしたって　何したって
No matter what I do, no matter what happens.
気持ちは同じなんだね
Our feelings are the same, aren't they?
ここだって　どこだって
Here, or anywhere.
想いは伝わるから
Because my feelings will reach you.
声にして　文字にして
Put it into words, put it into writing.
勇気出しておいで　咲いてよ
Gather your courage and come, let it bloom.
今日だって　いつだって
Today, or anytime.
ああ　愛してるも
Ah, even saying "I love you"...
Ah, ah, sweet stars...
隠さないでちゃんと教えて
Don't hide it, tell me everything.
君のこと全部を頂戴！
Give me all of you!
聞いて会いたいの　飛んでって
Listen, I want to see you, so fly away.
少し困るくらいにお願い
Please, just a little bit too much.
高鳴る心聞いてみて
Listen to my racing heart.
感じてほしいの
I want you to feel it.
会いたいはすぐ飛んでって
"I want to see you" flies away immediately.
少し困るくらいにおねだり
Begging you just a little bit too much.
ねぇ　ちゃんと聞いてみて　受け取って
Hey, listen carefully and accept it.
甘くとろけちゃうような時間を
A time that's so sweet it melts away.
隣にいたいから
Because I want to be by your side.
Ah, ah, sweet stars...
明日起きたら
When I wake up tomorrow
夢だと思おうかな
I might think it was a dream
いっぱいの光と音
With plenty of light and sound
私を連れ出して
Carry me away
ユーフォリア
歌：癒月ちょこ
作詞・作曲・編曲：渡辺ヒカル
Euphoria
Vocals: Yuzuki Choco
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Watanabe Hikaru
ふんわり世界は
The fluffy world is
甘くて優しくて恋焦がれた
Sweet, gentle, and I've longed for it
そんな感情初めて出会えたんだ
I encountered such a feeling for the first time
ねえ 聞かせてみて
Hey, let me hear it
あの歌で合図打って叩いて
Give the signal with that song and beat it out
んー告白だよ
Mmm, it's a confession
これからもよろしくね
Please treat me well from now on
隣歩んでいきたいな
I want to walk by your side
溢れそうな想いが
My overflowing feelings
こんなにも胸締め付けるんだ
Tighten my chest so much
どうしてなの
I wonder why
うまく言葉にできないよ アー
I can't put it into words well, ah
あなたが思うよりも
More than you think
私は幸せだよ
I am happy
この手の温もりが大切で愛おしい
This warmth in my hands is precious and dear
マイユーフォリア
My Euphoria
ふんわり世界は
The fluffy world is
広くて煌めいて褪せないな
Vast, sparkling, and doesn't fade
まだまだ知らない形
The shapes I still don't know
楽しいんだ
Are fun
ねえ 紡いでみよう
Hey, let's spin it out
続きの話をなぞって
Tracing the continuation of the story
んーありがとうだよ
Mmm, it's a "thank you"
お待たせとその先で
At the "sorry to keep you waiting" and beyond
あなた笑っていてくれて
You were smiling for me
ずるいよ アー
It's not fair, ah
お互い笑顔でいよう
Let's both stay smiling
終わりの日も変わらずに
Unchanging, even on the final day
これからのこと想うたび
Every time I think of what's to come
少しだけ泣けちゃうよ
I cry just a little bit
あれ この気持ち
Huh, this feeling...
言葉に出せないよ アー
I can't put it into words, ah
あなたといられるから
Because I can be with you
私は幸せだよ
I am happy
一瞬の足跡が特別で愛おしい
The footsteps of a single moment are special and dear
マイユーフォリア
My Euphoria
はい、ということで、
Yes, and so,
ここまでいかがだったでしょうかー！
how was it so far?!
たくさんチョコのお仲間たちが
So many of Choco's friends
来てくれました！
came!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
まあね、
Well,
いよいよライブも終盤ですが、
the live is finally reaching its final stages, but,
最後まで楽しんでいってください！
please enjoy yourselves until the end!
そしてそして、
And also,
このステージ、どうですかー！
how do you like this stage?!
ま、最初は、チョコでコーティングされた
Well, at first, it was a
シックでかっこいいお城だったんですけど、
chic and cool castle coated in chocolate,
みんなと歌って踊って、
but from singing and dancing with everyone,
その熱気と体温で、チョコが熱くなって溶けちゃいましたー！
the excitement and body heat made the chocolate hot and it melted!
見てよみんな、
Look everyone,
もうね、ビターチョコから...
it's already gone from bitter chocolate to...
ツインテでキュートなホワイトチョコに...
With twin-tails and cute white Choco...
雰囲気が早変わり！
The atmosphere quickly changes!
まあみんなはどっちの方が好みだったかは
Well, as for which one everyone preferred...
まあ後の感想でぜひぜひ教えてください。
Well, please let me know in the comments later.
まあね、この次はちょっとまだ、
Well, next is still...
ゲストパートなんですけど。
the guest part, though.
まあね、最後誰が
Well, I wonder who will be at the end...
どうなっちゃうのかな？
and what will happen?
まあちょっと予想してみてください！
Well, please try to guess!
それでは、最後ね。
So, the last one.
まあ最後と言っても全体では最後じゃないけど
Well, even though I say last, it's not the last overall.
ゲストパートは最後なんだ。
But it's the last guest part.
みんなちゃんと楽しんでる？
Are you all enjoying it?
いけてますかー？
Are you having a good time?
本当いつもお祝いしてくれてありがとう。
Thank you so much for always celebrating with me.
じゃあ、最後のゲストパート曲も盛り上がっていくぞ！
Well then, let's get hyped for the final guest part song!
それでは聴いてください。
Now, please listen.
どうぞ！
Here it is!
踊れオーケストラ / 曲 / 作詞・作曲: YASUHIRO(康寛)
Odore Orchestra / Song / Lyrics & Composition: YASUHIRO (Yasuhiro)
さあさあこの指に止まれ
Come on, come on, land on this finger
後悔後でしても知らないぞ
I won't care if you regret it later
音に飲まれて歌って踊ってみせるだけ
Just getting swallowed by the sound, singing and dancing
パンパン手を打ち鳴らして
Clap, clap, your hands together
そそそらしどんな五線譜も
So-so-so-la-si-do, any musical staff
音色をして今導き出すよ
Will have a timbre, I'll lead the way now
ショータイムは実は案外はがゆいもの
Showtime is actually unexpectedly frustrating
魔法のタクト空にかざすだけ
Just hold up the magic baton to the sky
おいでよ街を包み込んだ
Come here, the supernatural phenomenon
超常現象が
that enveloped the town,
夜空にほらこだまして退屈が泣き出す
Look, echoing in the night sky, boredom starts to cry
孤独な愛を埋めよう最終章素敵な舞台が
Let's fill the lonely love, the final chapter, a wonderful stage
君には聴こえた星に舞う旋律を
You heard it, the melody dancing to the stars
ワンツーサンシで泣いてた過去に負けない巡る力を
One-two-three-four, the power to circulate, not losing to the crying past
タンタン楽しいリズムで途切れない音をのせてタタン
Clap-clap, with a fun rhythm, carrying the continuous sound, ta-tan
愛と哀を描こうセプテット
Let's draw love and sorrow, Septet
忘れてた景色の向こうのその向こう
Beyond the scenery you'd forgotten, and beyond that
満ちた空の綻び
The rift in the full sky,
モノクロの望遠鏡
the monochrome telescope
待ったなしのぶっつけ本番で
No waiting, right into the live performance
奏でよう理想輝く幻想的蜃気楼
Let's play it, the ideal shining fantastical mirage
いつも目が合うあいつと手を繋ぎ踊ろう
Let's dance hand-in-hand with that person our eyes always meet
何度も泣いて泣いた心のエレジーを
The elegy of the heart that cried and cried many times
僕は聴こえただから今ここにいるんだ
I heard it, that's why I'm here now
ショータイムは実は案外悲しいもの
Showtime is actually unexpectedly sad
魔法の音色空に響かせて
Make the magic timbre resound in the sky
おいでよ街を包み込んだ
Come here, the supernatural phenomenon
超常現象が
that enveloped the town,
夜空にほらこだまして退屈が泣き出す
Look, echoing in the night sky, boredom starts to cry
愉快な歌を歌おう最終章...
Let's sing a happy song, the final chapter...
アンサン、アンサンブルも
Ensem-, even the ensemble
君は聞こえた？
Did you hear it?
星に舞う旋律を
The melody dancing in the stars
1 2 3 4で泣いてた
I was crying on 1, 2, 3, 4
過去に負けない巡る力を
A revolving power that won't lose to the past
タンタン楽しいリズムで
Tan-tan, with a fun rhythm
途切れない音を乗せて タタン
Adding sounds that never break, ta-tan
パンパン手を打ち鳴らして
Pan-pan, clap your hands
踊れ踊れオーケストラ
Dance, dance, orchestra!
バイバイ今夜はさよなら
Bye-bye, tonight is goodbye
次は君もステージで タタン
Next time, you'll be on stage too, ta-tan
さあさこの指にとまれ
Come now, land on this finger
後悔後でしても知らないぞ
I won't care if you regret it later
耳を澄まして
Listen closely
僕らと踊るだけ
And just dance with us
はーい、ちくまろ全員集合ー！
Hi! Chikumaro, everyone assemble!
わーい！いぇーい！
Yay! Yay!
いやー、今日はみんな、ちょこのために来てくれてありがとう！
Wow, thank you everyone for coming for Choco today!
ありがとう！こちらこそ！
Thank you! Same here!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
えー、ちょこ先誕生日おめでとー！
Um, Choco-sen, happy birthday!
おめでとー！
Happy birthday!
わーい、ケーキ食べた？ケーキ
Yay! Did you eat cake? Cake.
おめでとうございます
Congratulations.
いやーもう幸せだわ、ちょこ
Man, Choco is so happy right now.
ちょ、ケーキ持ってくればよかった、忘れちゃったわ
Wait, I should've brought a cake. I totally forgot.
あ、確かに。ケーキ忘れてた。
Ah, true. Forgot the cake.
いやまあまあ、今日はね、誕生日プレゼントに、ちょっとちょこに付き合ってもらってもいいですか？
Well, well, today, for my birthday present, could you hang out with Choco for a bit?
いいよー！もちろんだよ！いいともー！
Sure! Of course! You got it!
ちょっとちょこ、みんなとやりたいことがあって
Choco has something she wants to do with everyone.
お、何ー？何だい？
Oh, what is it? What?
あの、ちょっと一緒にグッズ告知…してもらえませんか？
Um, could you... help me announce my merchandise together?
グッズだってー！いいでしょう！
Merchandise! Okay!
ちょっとドキッとした今。いいでしょう。
I was a bit surprised just now. Sure.
一緒にポールダンスとかかと思った
I thought it was going to be pole dancing together.
ね、ポールダンス。やる気持ちで行ってたよね。
Yeah, pole dancing. I was totally ready for it.
え、ポールダンスもやりたい
Eh, I want to do pole dancing too.
ポールダンスいいかも
Pole dancing might be good.
やりたーい。ひまちゃんの見たい。
I want to. I want to see Hima-chan's.
ちょ、ちょこのチャンネルが危ないわこれ。やべー、やべー。
Wait, Choco's channel is in danger. Oh no, oh no.
わーい！ということで、では、今回も癒月ちょこ誕生日記念グッズが出まーす！
Yay! So, then, this time too, Yuzuki Choco birthday commemorative merchandise is coming out!
いぇーい！でまーす！出たー！
Yay! It's out! It's out!
それでは一つずつ見ていきましょう。まず一つ目は、こちら！ワイドラバーマット！
Let's look at them one by one. First up is this! Wide Rubber Mat!
かわいいー！おー！
Cute! Oh!
はい、こちらのね、イラストはNardack先生が描いていただきました！
Yes, this illustration was drawn by Nardack-sensei!
いぇーい！かわいいねー！
Yay! It's cute!
いや、Nardack先生大好き。かっこいい。確かに。
Wow, I love Nardack-sensei. Cool. True.
ちょっと毎年ちょこの誕生日はね、Nardack先生に描いていただいてて
Every year for Choco's birthday, I have Nardack-sensei draw it.
いいなー。去年のもよかったし。
Nice. Last year's was good too.
よかった！今年のんもめちゃくちゃかっこいい。
It was good! This year's is super cool too.
いやそうなんですよ
Yeah, it really is.
今回はね、可愛いちょことカッコいいちょこの二人がね、ちょっと背中合わせになってるイラストなんですけど
This time, it's an illustration with cute Choco and cool Choco back-to-back.
あー！両方楽しめるやつだ！いい！エモい！買います！
Ah! The one where you can enjoy both. Good! Emotional! I'll buy it!
買います！買います！
I'll buy it! I'll buy it!
そう、ホワイトちょことダークちょこ、二人とも愛してください
Yes, please love both White Choco and Dark Choco.
ええなー！えーど！食べていいですか？えーど！
Nice! Great! Can I eat them? Great!
はい、そしてそしてー、次のグッズが…はい、ちょこめいと法被でーす！
Yes, and and next, the next merchandise is... yes, Chocomate Happi!
おー！すごーい！いいなー！
Oh! Amazing! Nice!
めっちゃ近く…背中の大きく『ちょこめいと』って書いてあって
So close... It says 'Chocomate' big on the back.
表にはね、ちょっと癒月ちょことかいうこの刺繍がまたね、かっこよく、いい感じに
On the front, there's this embroidery of 'Yuzuki Choco' and such, cool and in a nice way.
すごい！刺繍なんだ。
Amazing! It's embroidery.
そう、推しグッズとして是非
Yes, please use it as fan merchandise.
すごいねこれ、直筆で縫ったのこれ？
Amazing, did you sew this by hand?
ちょ、ちょっとそこは…手出しできないんで…
Um, a little bit... I can't put my hand into that...
そこはやばいです。心あるけどね。直筆縫製みたいな。裁縫？
That's dangerous. There's heart in it though. Like hand-sewn. Sewing?
直筆刺繍はハードル高すぎるわ。一体いくら上がるんだ、それ。
Hand-sewn embroidery is too high a hurdle. How much would the price go up for that?
5万円ぐらいで売るしかないぞ、そんなん。確かに確かに。
You'd have to sell it for like 50,000 yen. True, true.
はい、そして次は、はい！ちょこの角カチューシャでございまーす！
Yes, and next is, yes! Choco's Horn Headband!
おー！欲しい欲しい！なかったね！
Oh! I want it, I want it! We didn't have that!
え、かわいいー！
Eh, cute!
いやそうなんです、これ全部スパンコールになってて
Yes, that's right, this is all covered in sequins.
キラキラだー！
It's sparkly!
そう、つけてるだけでちょこの角の存在感が可愛くね、つけれちゃうという
Yes, just by wearing it, you can cute-ly wear the presence of Choco's horns.
誰でも！誰でもちょこ先になれる！欲しい欲しい！
Anyone! Anyone can become Choco-sen! I want it, I want it!
そう、誰でもちょこになれちゃう角カチューシャでございまーす！
Yes, it's a Horn Headband where anyone can become Choco!
ちくまろでちょこになりましょう、みんなで。4人ちょこになりましょう、じゃあ。
Let's become Choco as Chikumaro, everyone. Let's become 4 Chocos then.
4ちょこになりましょう。これでちくまろやろう。
Let's become 4 Chocos. Let's be Chikumaro with this.
ちょこの角カチューシャ
Choco's Horn Headband
え、めっちゃいいこれ。可愛い！
Whoa, this is great. So cute!
そしてそして！今年もございます！
And, and! We have this again this year!
ボイス
Voice
ちょこ書き下ろし台本の耳舐めASMR！
An ear-licking ASMR with a script written by Choco!
おいおいおい！耳舐め？！
Whoa whoa whoa! Ear-licking?!
え、エドってこと？！
Wait, does that mean it's lewd?!
いや、任せてくださいよ！
Don't worry, just leave it to me!
舐めはエドだよ！
Licking is definitely lewd!
えっ、何を舐めるの？！
Wait, what are you licking?!
ちょっと、ひまちゃんにはまだ早いかな？
Wait, maybe it's too early for Hima-chan?
びっくりしちゃった。
You startled me.
耳を舐める？
Licking the ear?
そうです。耳をジュルジュルしちゃいます！
That's right. I'm going to slurp on those ears!
いいんですか？！
Is that allowed?!
許されているのがおかしいよ！
It's crazy that they allow this!
いやいや、いいだろこれは！
No, no, it's totally fine!
「ならでは」ってことか、ちょこ先生。
I guess it's something only Choco-sensei can do.
ちょっと買いますわ。
I'm going to buy this.
なんで、聞き惚れてるのルイちゃん？！
Wait, why are you so captivated, Lui-chan?!
お願いします、ちょっと。
Please, I'm begging you.
はい！そしてですね！今回はフルセットもございます！
Yes! And! We also have a full set this time!
誕生日記念フルセット
Birthday Commemorative Full Set
フルセット購入特典として、ポストカードを...
As a bonus for buying the full set, a postcard...
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
ちょこの直筆サイン入りのものが届きます！
...personally signed by Choco will be delivered!
さらに！フルセット購入特典がもう一つあります！
And! There's one more full set purchase bonus!
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PRカード
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PR Card
ホロライブ公式カードゲームで使用できるカードがもう一枚ついてきます！
Another card for the Hololive Official Card Game is included!
え、何それ！すご！
Wait, what's that?! Amazing!
推しアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードです！
It's an 'Oshi Holomen' key card to show off your favorite!
すごーい！
That's incredible!
カードは日本語版のみとなりますので、ご了承下さい。
Please note that the card is available in Japanese only.
そして、書き下ろし台本の特別ボイスも付いてきます！
And it also comes with a special scripted voice!
さらに付いちゃう？！
Even more bonuses?!
また耳舐めボイスがあるの？！
Is there another ear-licking voice?!
次はどこ舐めてもらえるんですか？！
Where are you going to lick next?!
もちろんもちろん！ナメナメしちゃいます！
Of course, of course! I'll be licking it all!
良くないだろ！
That's not right!
最高だよ！
It's the best!
記念グッズは配信終了後より販売開始となりますので...
Commemorative goods will go on sale after this stream...
概要欄のURLと、Xの方をチェックしてみて下さい！
...so please check the URL in the description and my X!
でもね、ちょこ、今年一番嬉しかったのが...
But you know, for Choco, the thing I'm happiest about this year...
こうして皆が配信に来てくれたことが嬉しかったです！
...is that everyone came to my stream like this!
いやいや、こちらこそだよ！
No, no, we should be the ones thanking you!
一緒にダンスできて楽しかったです！
I had so much fun dancing together!
今年もデコボコやりたい！
I want to do more 'Dekoboko' things this year too!
今年も一緒に楽しみましょう！
Let's enjoy this year together too!
それでは、次が最後の曲です。
Now, the next song will be the last one.
聴いてください。
Please listen.
はぁ〜、いい天気。
Ahh, what nice weather.
保健室のベッドでお昼寝したい。
I want to take a nap on the health room bed.
冬休み　許されない
Winter break isn't allowed
保健室は神聖なの
The health room is sacred
サボってる？　ちょっとだけ
Slacking off? Just a little bit
誰も来ない　やる気出ない
Nobody's coming, I have no motivation
ちょこせんせーしょん
Choco Sensation
ちょこちょこ　せんせーしょん
Choco Choco Sensation
このままじゃ私ダメみたい
At this rate, I'm going to be useless
ひまちゃんうとうと　2回目のあくび
Hima-chan dozing off, the second yawn
おやすみなさい
Good night
ごめんなさい　少しだけ寝かせて　先生もシャットダウン
I'm sorry, let me sleep just a bit, even Teacher is shutting down
夢見る　ふわふわ　ずっとこうして眠りたい
Dreaming, fluffy, I want to keep sleeping like this forever
ありがとう　ねこぱか　ちょっと休憩してるだけ
Thank you, Nekopaka, I'm just taking a little break
油断大敵ですね
You shouldn't let your guard down
急に君が来るなんて
For you to show up so suddenly
ねえ　どこか悪いの？
Hey, do you feel unwell somewhere?
何か期待しているのかな
Are you expecting something?
揺らぐ心　巡る感情　ちょこちょこせんせーしょん
A swaying heart, swirling emotions, Choco Choco Sensation
癒やされたい　甘えたいと　言いたいよ　ちょこせんせーしょん
I want to be healed, I want to be spoiled, I want to say it, Choco Sensation
君の視線　君の体温　分かってても恋は計れない
Your gaze, your warmth, even knowing them, love cannot be measured
元気なのにため息出ちゃう
Even though I'm healthy, a sigh escapes me
もしかして何か甘い病？
Could this be some kind of sweet sickness?
ドキドキするまで動けないから　ドキドキ運んできて my student
I can't move until my heart starts racing, so bring that excitement, my student
冬休み　また来たの
Winter break has come again
保健室は神聖なの
The health room is sacred
サボってた？　ちょっとだけ
Was I slacking off? Just a little bit
やっぱり君にいてほしい
After all, I want you to be here
週末 お休み なんだよ
Weekend? A day off? What's that?
家飲み 最高
Home drinking is the best!
引きこもり 最高
Being a shut-in is the best!
もちろん 本命
Of course, my favorite.
チャイムが鳴ったら即行きます
If the bell rings, I'll go immediately.
さあ 全てを見せて
Now, show me everything.
ジャッジ不可能な出来事
Unpredictable events,
何を隠してるの
What are you hiding?
鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
I can hear your racing heartbeat.
揺れる心めくるシャツを
My swaying heart, flipping through my shirt.
絶好調を保ってる現状
Currently in top form.
愛されたい 頼られたい
Want to be loved, want to be relied on,
オトメチョコセンセーション
Otome Choco-Sensation!
君の重み 君の匂い
Your weight, your scent,
分かっても愛は測れない
Even if I know, love can't be measured.
大好きだから溜息ついちゃう
Because I love you so much, I can't help but sigh.
やっぱりそれは恋の病
As expected, it's lovesickness.
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart thumps,
ときめき運んで
so bring me some excitement,
My student
幕を開けたって
Even if the curtain rises,
この世界だって
even in this world,
みんな癒しが
everyone needs some healing,
必要だから
because it's necessary.
チョコチョコセンセーション
Choco Choco-Sensation! Yay!
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to spoil you, too.
揺らぐ心めぐる感情
My swaying heart, racing emotions,
口溶け甘いセンセーション
A sweet-melting sensation.
癒されたい 甘えていたい
Want to be healed, want to be pampered,
オトメチョコセンセーション
Otome Choco-Sensation!
君の視線 君の体温
Your gaze, your body heat,
分かっても愛は測れない
Even if I know, love can't be measured.
元気なのに溜息ついちゃう
Even though I'm fine, I can't help but sigh.
もしかしてもっと手遅れ?
Maybe it's already too late?
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart thumps,
ときめき運んで
so bring me some excitement,
My student
チョコチョコセンセーション
Choco Choco-Sensation! Yay!
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to spoil you, too.
ん...
Nnn...
ふあぁ...
Huaaa...
おら ばんちょー 起きた?
Hey, Bancho. You awake?
ばんじゃ... 寝てたぁ...
Banja... I was sleeping...
ん... どこや... ジム所?
Where are we? The office?
ジム所...
The office...
さっきチョコ先生とダンスしてた気がするなぁ...
I feel like I was just dancing with Choco-sensei...
ダンス?
Dancing?
ばんちょー さっきまで寝てたよ
Bancho, you were sleeping until just now.
えー? そうなんだー... 夢かぁ...
Really? So it was a dream...
そんなことより
More importantly...
お寿司食べに行かない?
Wanna go get some sushi?
あー行く! 回らないお寿司!
Oh, I'm in! High-end sushi!
行こう行こう!
Let's go, let's go!
お寿司だー!
Sushi!
お寿司ー!
癒月ちょこ 生誕祭 2025
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2025